<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
	<channel>
		<title>Stuff and Things</title>
		<link>https:&#x2F;&#x2F;mcluck90.github.io</link>
		<description>A descent into the mind of Mike Cluck</description>
		<generator>Gutenberg</generator>
		<language>en</language>
		<atom:link href="https:&#x2F;&#x2F;mcluck90.github.io&#x2F;rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
		<lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
			<item>
				<title>Writing something on the side</title>
				<pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<link>https:&#x2F;&#x2F;mcluck90.github.io&#x2F;writing-something-on-the-side&#x2F;</link>
				<guid>https:&#x2F;&#x2F;mcluck90.github.io&#x2F;writing-something-on-the-side&#x2F;</guid>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;This article is going to be all over the place. I&#x27;ve talked to a lot of people recently who seem to be struggling with finding a project to work on in their spare time. This is a rough compilation of my thoughts on the matter.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Side projects are a great way to hone your skills, build something to help yourself, or just pump up your resume. They also, rarely, come out of nowhere. It&#x27;s not often that you&#x27;re just struck with the perfect idea of what you want to build. It does happen but I&#x27;ve got a number of ideas and approaches which may help you get that kick-start when you&#x27;re lacking in the inspiration department. I&#x27;ve listed these in order of ease. The earlier things will be easier to get into and complete. The later ones will take more work but will reap greater rewards if completed. Without further ado, here&#x27;s 4 ways to get started on a side project.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
<br /><a href="https:&#x2F;&#x2F;mcluck90.github.io&#x2F;writing-something-on-the-side&#x2F;#continue-reading">Continue Reading</br></description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Abusing Proxies for DSLs</title>
				<pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<link>https:&#x2F;&#x2F;mcluck90.github.io&#x2F;abusing-proxies-for-dsls&#x2F;</link>
				<guid>https:&#x2F;&#x2F;mcluck90.github.io&#x2F;abusing-proxies-for-dsls&#x2F;</guid>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Disclaimer:&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt; Writing code like this can lead to both the browser and your coworkers hating you. Code like this can be very difficult to test and is going to be slower than just writing code with good old-fashioned functions and sweat. Older browsers will not run this code at all. Consider yourself warned.&lt;&#x2F;small&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
<br /><a href="https:&#x2F;&#x2F;mcluck90.github.io&#x2F;abusing-proxies-for-dsls&#x2F;#continue-reading">Continue Reading</br></description>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>